I waited a long time, yeah
came
I just broke up too
Kang Jae-rang
We've been watching since a while ago
let's go
Oh sorry how much I slept
I couldn't sleep. Sleep more.
You must have been very tired.
It's okay
It's not me who's having a hard time
You are the ones who protect humans.
All I'm doing is looking for demons
That's all
Oh my gosh
The ability you gave me is special
When demons enter the barrier
soul stone
What can be detected and found
There's only you
Will this be possible in the future?
You couldn’t sleep today either.
It's not about your abilities
The hanger clearly responded as well.
I'm not sure what's what
The evil spirit that appeared this time was
I feel the energy, but it quickly disappears.
And I don't know why
keep me going
I feel like I'm being watched
don't worry too much
everyone
Trying to catch the devil
no matter what happens
Because I will protect you
me actually
I started praying
You said that, Maruk is also human.
After praying for a long time
I received the power of God
Me too, like Maruk
able to subdue evil spirits
When you gain strength
You'll be able to stay with an angel
Then I'm no longer with you
You don't have to stay
don't do it
Don't do anything useless
What
You change because of me
so reckless
Don't even pray
I don't like it
What I like is you now
Ogi
between us
Let's just be honest with everyone.
Don't talk nonsense
Now I'm telling you
I think they will understand us
If it were that simple
Why couldn't I say anything until now?
Then how long like this
I'm going to meet you in hiding
so don't do anything
If you pray rather than pray
Stop it
I want to be an angel
you don't know
with musical instruments
How dangerous is it to fight?
It's dangerous to meet like this
Same thing
Kangji knows about our relationship.
Miriam
trust me
God ignores my prayers
angels
us
Even if you don't understand
Nothing changes
my heart won't change
soon
The black moon rises
how much
Soon the gates of hell will open
Inform Odae
disperse the angels
Have you seen
I'm praying
You said that, Marok is also human.
After praying for a long time
I received the power of God
I'm like Marok too
evil spirits
If you gain the power to overpower
You'll be able to stay with an angel
Then I'm no longer with you
You don't have to stay
In the meantime
The body that wandered around without my attention
Is it you
You've been stealing for me all this time.
I
A little bit with other humans
I thought it would be different
Why are you doing such a foolish thing?
There's no way God will hear your prayers
You are a human who can't do anything
It's just that
No way
god is human
To such a world
balance can be lost
I'll give you absolute power
Think about it, if you want to meet the future
There's only one way
A human body as weak as it is now
Throw away
A power stronger than angels
What you get
you and god
Not obeying angels
Just make them follow you
who are you
Humans believe in your gods
I call it light
I
They call it darkness
coming
I'll give you a new life
why do i
tell me
why should i listen to you
Him
It's his doing
You were human
born again
I forgot how I got my strength
The scattered angels are at the gates of hell
I found the location
They're gathering one by one
I can't deal with everyone
If only Mir's dragon source was taken away,
They won't be able to join forces either.
Even if I reach the gates of hell
You won't be able to do anything
If we don't stop it soon, we
Ugh
Don't be mistaken
you have no power
Just lend your body to the darkness
petty magic
He's just a priest who uses things like that.
have the same purpose
Thinking we're in the same position
I don't think the order is a bit wrong.
The topic is always next to me
Don't talk too much, listen carefully.
you just
Living as I tell you
All you have to do is save your life
From now on
my shadow
Even nearby
Don't come, hold your breath from far away
I follow you
It's been a while
I came alone
Why did you betray us?
You're asking why we betrayed
Because I was bored
uh
made by god
I'm bored of being locked in a fence
Pirne
I go to the mountain according to my own will
I just chose to live
Nothing has changed
what are you doing
without killing quickly
Let's go back
Taesan will definitely help you.
Because it's not too late now
If you ask God for forgiveness, he will forgive you
I've prayed countless days
It was your god who abandoned me
Distinguish between angels and humans
Your dirty discipline
ruined everything for me
This is my last request
Let's go back
come
Even if you think about the future
Just stay like that
This is the time I sent it to you because of the future.
Because it's the last time
You can't do it, sister.
No no no no
no
No way
It's my sister
It's Miru
ha
It's really dangerous alone
Ha, I'm going crazy, ha.
Oh what
Like a fool
Ah
Ah ah
I'm shaking
why again
I came back here
I remember
You're back
Because everything has changed
I don't even know where I am
The only thing I remember was this place.
I'll call the captain.
We run away like we did back then
Because I don’t think it’s good for everyone.
In the end, will I be trapped again?
then
why did you do that
Why betray us all
Betrayal to the side of the instruments
That's right
It must have been a betrayal to the good angels
I'm just you
Done
What good does it do now?
Name ugh
let's go
Grab that too
Uncle, for a long time
I lived a very long time
We have to protect good people too.
I am human
It's been a long time since I stopped protecting
you know
If the instruments come, then
You will protect me again, right?
Be prepared to prevent damage
give outside
Please refrain from activities.
I ask you to do so.
and continues
It's really not a fuss
Now stand up
What should we do about the future? Let’s build it quickly.
I can smell a confession from the other side of the captain.
They say you shouldn’t kill evil spirits.
They say you can turn them back into humans
Okay
I'll live well
live well
This way
ha
The child's boss borrowed it
It's all about money
I believe it has been taken care of.
Why did you come here?
Ha, let’s come in, boss.
You're not here right now.
I didn't ask the boss.
No, you really aren't there.
We have to go in
come next time next time
This is also very expensive
I can't get this
uh
Heo Yangsu's brother
Is this whiskey or something?
Ah, all liquor is whiskey.
When my brother was at school, I only studied alcohol.
It's one person
I went to your school too, then
Well, all over the country
one
I worked hard for about fifteen years.
Oh, it's been a long time
Ah, it’s the doctor’s family.
Seohan: Should we stop drinking?
Why is the drink delicious?
Why is it so loud?
Go out, your brother, brother.
who
child
Hey, what is this taste?
Come on brother
Ah Nice Punch
Hyeong-gyu is a boxing champion.
It's no big deal, bro.
Ah
uh uh
Uh uh uh
Uh uh uh uh uh uh
Uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh
uh uh
Ah ah
Ugh
Wow
Oh where are you
Where are you?
Wow, Angel boss
I'm glad, I'm glad, it's strange, uh uh
Look over there, look, uh uh uh
uh
Who are you looking at? Who are you talking about?
Uh, I'm going, uh uh uh
Wow
Wow wow
Woo
Kangji, there is nothing more, yes, there is nothing more, captain.
Brother, from today
I will treat you as my big brother.
No, don't take it. Yes.
No, there are private loans around me
There are a lot of juniors who can write.
There are a lot, brother
Oh that's good
Because the situation is bad now
Please get in quickly
Yeah hey let's go quickly
Yes, let's go in, brother.
yes thank you bro
Please go in
Ugh
Ah
Let's go in
Kang Jae, I'm sure you're going this way.
Yeah I'm sure
The pendant is also responding
Above all, I come
There's no way I'll forget the smell
Ha, this is it.
where is the future
The future is dangerous
Samin took the future
You've probably already gone to the gates of hell
Must have a future soul
You will gain true strength
that again
What can seal the gates of hell
You guys have the only power
I have a favor to ask
Give me some time to recover
Earn it
I'll take care of the rest
How dare these people tell me where this is?
Hano
Yes my kids
Taesung this
Guys
It's a bit strange
How did I wake up?
I feel like I'm being manipulated by three people.
Hey everyone, summon your weapons
captain
Anyway, they are our kids.
We have to stop it first
I have to deal with Samin first.
Stop it for now
No, but that
No, but what should I do?
The captain said to stop it.
Stop it for now
Let's go
I'll follow you soon
ha
Anu
yes
Ah
everyone is okay
I can't take Yang Mi because she's in my sight.
Everyone is so strong
Please draw my attention, Donghui.
Stop it until the end somehow
If you are with me
You can have stronger power than now
No one will be able to stop it
This is it
Will this be the answer?
Blurred senses
This is a familiar illusion of an American drama
Yesterday becomes a knife that stabs me
I can't trust anyone
My heart that I lean on and cover is frozen
It broke me who hid my desires
My heart is a new drum
Yes, my heart is a new drum
tag
Foot, foot, foot, foot, if you're scared now
rattle rattle rattle
If you peel me off quickly, I will tie your neck.